{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Rènshì" ,
      "answer": "认识"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gāoxìng",
      "answer": "高兴"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kěyǐ" ,
      "answer": "可以"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jìnlái",
      "answer": "进来"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qǐng",
      "answer": "请"
    },
    {
      "question": "Péngyǒu",
      "answer": "朋友"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jìzhě",
      "answer": "记者"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qǐngwèn",
      "answer": "请问"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xìng",
      "answer": "姓"
    },
    {
      "question": "Guìxìng",
      "answer": "贵姓"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiào",
      "answer": "叫"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiānshēng",
      "answer": "先生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǔyán",
      "answer": "语言"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéyuàn",
      "answer": "学院"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xué",
      "answer": "学"
    },
    {
      "question": "De",
      "answer": "的"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéshēng",
      "answer": "学生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shénme",
      "answer": "什么"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéxí",
      "answer": "学习"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hànyǔ",
      "answer": "汉语"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīngguó",
      "answer": "英国"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiānádà",
      "answer": "加拿大"
    },
    {
      "question": "Měiguó",
      "answer": "美国"
    }
  ]
}
